爸爸
Hi, Daddy.
见到你真高兴
You're a sight for sore eyes.
-还好吗  -是的
- Doing okay? - Yeah.
是的  先生
Yes, sir.
-遇上麻烦了吗  -没有
- Any trouble? - No.
-你遇上了  -对
- You had some. - Yeah.
有点吧
A little.
卡萝尔  给我吧
Carol, I'll take that.
m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0
m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172
m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35
本字幕由人人影视字幕组翻译
禁止用作任何商业盈利行为
翻译  送男神
翻译  送蘑菇
翻译  送小h
翻译  重案组李Sir
翻译  熊爷虐行尸
翻译  送马勺
听译  CS送小明
校对  冰蓝
翻译/校对  老哥五一见  送小孩
时间轴  涛涛 送小森
时间轴  送雪妞
后期  、青衣
特效/后期  吉吉
总监  送小孩爱猴小鞋
行尸走肉
第四季  第十六集
本季终
按1到10算  你有多饿
How hungry are you, scale of one to 10?
15.
28.
好吧  有一阵子了
Yeah. Well, it's been a while.
我去看看圈套
I'm gonna go check the snares.
我能和你一起去吗
Can I go with you?
不然你怎么学技术呢
Well, how else are you gonna learn?
你也来
Hey, you, too.
我们再待一两天
We'll stay another day or two.
休息会儿
Get some more rest.
痊愈了吗
Finish healing up?
我快痊愈了
I'm almost there.
我们很近了  对吧
We're close now, right?
离终点站吗
To Terminus?
-是的  -很近了
- Yeah. - We are.
到那里后
When we get there,
我们要告诉他们吗
are we gonna tell them?
告诉他们什么
Tell them what?
我们经历的一切
Everything that's happened to us.
做过的一切
All the stuff we've done.
我们要告诉他们真相吗
Are we gonna tell them the truth?
我们要告诉他们我们是谁
We're gonna tell them who we are.
但你要怎么说呢  我是说...
But how do you say that? I mean...
我们到底是谁
who are we?
有了
There you go.
是只小的
It's a small one.
也能凑合
It'll do.
这是个简单的活结
So, this is just a simple slipknot.
在绳子的两头打结
Tie one on both ends,
然后把一端系在树枝上
then you tighten one side to a branch.
你能看到这地面
Now, you see how the ground here
有点像漏斗形的
is sort of like a funnel shape?
-这是条小路吗  -对
- It's a trail? - That's right.
你要把套索放在这里
That's where you want to set the noose.
用叶子遮住
So you hide it with leaves.
在旁边摆上木棍
Then you put sticks all around it
经过的动物必须走这条路
so any animals going by have to run this way
刚好踩中圈套
right into the trap.
救命
Help!
-快救命  -卡尔
- Somebody help! - Carl.
-卡尔  停下  卡尔  -后退  后退
- Carl, stop! Carl! - Get back! Back!
救命
Help!
走开  后退
Get away! Get back!
救命  来人救救我
Help! Somebody help!
救救我
Help me!
走开
Get away!
不
No!
走开
Get away!
-救命  来人救救我  -我们救不了他
- Help! Somebody help! - We can't help him.
不要  不要
No! No! No! No!
我们得走了
We've got to go.
早
Morning.
一切还好吗
Everything okay?
是啊  只是想要人帮点忙
Yeah, just want a little help with something.
几点了
What time is it?
我已经没有时间概念了
I never know what time it is anymore.
自从我把表给了格伦以后
Ever since I gave Glenn my watch,
对我来说都是当下时刻
it's always right now to me.
是早上
It's early.
进来吧
He's decent.
-早  -早
- Morning. - Morning.
贝丝会照看朱迪思
Bethy's gonna take Judith.
我们要干嘛去
What are we doing?
待会儿你就知道了
You'll see.
你用不上那个
You're not going to need that.
枪只会碍事儿
It'll just get in the way.
走吧
Let's go.
这条路上可能会有房子
Thought maybe there'd be some houses down this way.
可能有商店
Maybe even a store.
这周围总会有点吃的
There's got to be some food around here somewhere.
看啊
Hey, look.
这兔子太小了
That was one small rabbit.
至少有吃的
It was something.
我们得感谢它
Got to hand it to the thing.
味道好极了
It traveled well.
似乎现在我们只会谈这一个话题
Have you noticed that's all we talk about anymore?
食物
Food.
我都忘了风餐露宿的感觉了
I forgot what this feels like.
我也是
Me, too.
希望我们能尽快再次忘记
I hope we're able to forget again soon.
我们快到了
We're close.
再坚持一天就好
Just got to make it through another day.
既然那里的人在收人
If folks there are taking people in,
他们一定很强大
they have to be strong.
他们一定有一套体系
They have to have a system.
也不知道是真是假
I wonder if the whole thing's legit.
我们就收过人
We let people in.
确实
We did.
总督也是
So did the Governor.
是啊  总是如此  对吧
Yeah, it's always the same, isn't it?
最后才会知道真相
Don't get to know until we know.
可能这个地方都不存在了
Maybe this place isn't even there anymore.
哎呦喂
Oh, dearie me.
你死定了  混蛋
You screwed up, asshole.
你听见了吗  你死定了
You hear me? You screwed up.
今天是算账的日子  先生
Today is a day of reckoning, sir.
了结恩怨
Restitution.
整个宇宙又会回到平衡的状态
A balancing of the whole damn universe.
还好在新年前夜
Shit, and I was thinking of turning in for the night
我没有着急睡觉
on New Year's Eve.
谁跟我一起来倒数新年
Now who's gonna count down the ball dropper with me, huh?
十
10 Mississippi.
九
Nine Mississippi.
-八  -乔
- Eight Mississippi. - Joe!
-等等  -我刚数到八  达里尔
- Hold up. - You're stopping me on eight, Daryl.
等等
Just hold up.
这个人把卢杀死了  没什么好谈的
This is the guy that killed Lou, so we got nothing to talk about.
现在我们最不缺的就是时间
The thing about nowadays is we got nothing but time.
你有什么要说的  达里尔
Say your piece, Daryl.
这些人
These people,
你放他们走
you're gonna let 'em go.
他们是好人
These are good people.
我觉得卢不会同意这一点
Now, I think Lou would disagree with you on that.
当然了  我得替他说话  因为
I'll, of course, have to speak for him and all
你的朋友在厕所里把他勒死了
'cause your friend here strangled him in a bathroom.
你想要报仇  我明白
You want blood, I get it.
那就冲我来吧
Take it from me, man.
来吧
Come on.
这男的杀了我们的朋友
This man killed our friend.
你却说他是个好人
You say he's good people.
看见没  这就是一个谎言
See, now that right there is a lie.
是个谎言
It's a lie!
-拜托  -不
- Come on. - No!
教训他  伙计们  好好教训他
Teach him, fellas. Teach him all the way.
-不要  -过来  小正太
- No! - Come here, boy.
你放开他
You leave him be!
等下就轮到你了  好好等着吧
You'll get yours. You just wait your turn.
听着  是我干的  只有我
Listen, it was me. It was just me.
瞧  这就对了  这才他妈不是谎言
See, now that's right. That's not some damn lie.
我们能解决这个的  我们是通情达理的人
Look, we can settle this. We're reasonable men.
首先  我们要把达里尔打死
First, we're gonna beat Daryl to death.
然后我们再处理那个女的
Then we'll have the girl.
之后处理那个男孩
Then the boy.
最后我把你杀了  这样我们就扯平了
Then I'm gonna shoot you and then we'll be square.
放开他
Let him go.
别扭了
Stop your squirming.
放开他
Let him go.
我制住他了
I got him.
现在情况要严重得多了
Oh, it's gonna be so much worse now.
来吧  起来
Come on, get up!
来吧  让我看看你有啥本事
Come on. Let's see what you got.
-放开他  不然我就...  -过来
- Get away from him before I-- - Huh? Right over here.
我看你能怎样  蠢货
What the hell are you gonna do now, sport?
我会杀了他的
I'll kill him.
我会...我会杀了他的
I'll-- I'll kill him!
放开那男孩
Let the boy go.
他是我的
He's mine.
别过来  别...求你...
Stay back. Stay-- please--
就这儿
Here.
是什么
What is?
那些林子里的野猪
Those feral pigs in the forest,
很容易驯养
it doesn't take much to domesticate them.
就和我们见过的那些马一样
Same with the horses we've seen.
我们有种子  我们能自己种粮食
We have seeds. We can grow our own food.
是时候开始种地了
It's time we started planting.
好的
Okay.
我自己可搞不定
Can't do it myself.
我得到那边去
I got to go out there.
去外面找补给  去围栏那儿帮忙
Go on runs, be at the fences.
我教你怎么务农
I teach you how to do this.
然后你去教卡尔
You teach Carl.
我们会在这里待上一阵子的
We're going to be here a while.
他们需要我
They need me.
我们已经到这里两个月了
We've been here two months.
你把这里运营了起来
You've made it work.
战争已经结束了  瑞克
The war is over, Rick.
不  这我们可不知道
No, we don't know that.
我是在说你的事
I'm talking about you.
我要说出来
I'm saying it,
我要说清楚
and I'm saying this,
你不让卡尔出去  这很好
you pull Carl back from going out there, fine.
-他射杀了那个男孩  -是的  我知道
- He shot that boy. - Yeah, I know.
他需要他的父亲
He needs his father.
他需要他的父亲给他指明道路
He needs his father to show him the way.
你要给他指明什么样的道路呢
What way are you going to show him?
他会用枪
He can shoot,
我们都知道
we know that.
但他今后的人生怎么过
What's his life going to be?
你又怎么过
What's yours?
这一切
All this.
我之所以对你说这些
I'm just saying everything
是因为我亏欠你
because I owe you.
我们大家都亏欠你
We all owe you.
我们可以把这里变好
We can make this better now.
这里变好
Things changing in here
外面又不会变好
doesn't change things out there.
确实
No, it doesn't.
但此时此刻  我们身处这里
But we're here today, right now.
这是重新开始的好机会
This is a good place to start.
马上要外出了
There's a run soon.
我必须走了
I got to go.
不  你不必
No, you don't.
省点水留着喝吧
We should save it to drink.
你看不到自己  他可以看到
You can't see yourself, he can.
我不知道他们是什么样的人
I didn't know what they were.
你怎么会跟他们在一起
How'd you wind up with them?
我和贝丝在一起
I was with Beth.
我们逃了出来
We got out together.
一起待了一段时间
I was with her for a while.
她死了吗
Is she dead?
她只是不见了
She's just gone.
在那之后
After that,
他们就找到了我
that's when they found me.
我知道他们很坏  但
I mean, I knew they were bad,but ...
他们有一套准则
they had a code.
很简单
It was simple.
很蠢
Stupid,
但挺有用
but it was something.
这就足够了
It was enough.
而且你孤身一人
And you were alone.
他们说他们在找一个人
Said they were looking for some guy.
昨晚  他们说找到他了
Last night they said they spotted him.
我正在犹豫  我本打算离开
I was hanging back. I was gonna leave.
但还是留下了
But I stayed.
就在那时  我看到了你们仨
That's when I saw it was you three.
你也看到了我
Right when you saw me.
我不知道
I didn't know
他们会那样做
what they could do.
这不怪你  达里尔
It's not on you, Daryl.
这不是你的错
It's not on you.
此时此刻  你跟我们重聚
You being back with us here, now,
这才是最重要的
that's everything.
你是我的兄弟
You're my brother.
你昨晚的举动
Hey, what you did last night...
换做任何人都会那样做
anybody would have done that.
不  未必
No, not that.
你失控了
Something happened.
那完全不是你
That ain't you.
达里尔  你看到我对泰尔西做了什么
Daryl, you saw what I did to Tyreese.
虽不尽然  但那就是我
It ain't all of it, but that's me.
这就是我和卡尔依然活着的原因
That's why I'm here now. That's why Carl is.
我想保证他安然无恙
I want to keep him safe.
我只在乎这一点
That's all that matters.
你还好吗
You okay?
是的
Yeah.
我也很好
I'm okay.
我知道
I know.
你怎么知道
How?
因为我也很好
'Cause I'm okay, too.
终点站
我们离得很近了
We're getting close.
日落前能到
Be there before sundown.
现在朝树林里走吧
Now we head through the woods.
还没搞清楚他们的底细
We don't know who they are.
行
All right.
终点站
大家分散开
We all spread out,
踩下点  打探一下情况
watch for a while, see what we see,
做好准备
and get ready.
别走得太远
We all stay close.
你想跟我一起吗
You want to stick with me?
不必了
It's all right.
为什么不跟你老爸一块儿
Why didn't you go with your dad?
当我跟你说起安德烈时
When I told you about Andre,
你都没问过他是怎么死的
you never asked how he died.
我知道原因
I knew why.
是啊  但...
Yeah, but ...
过程也很重要
the how is important.
我们当时去了难民营
We went to a refugee camp.
有安德烈和我的男友麦克
Andre and my boyfriend Mike,
他是安德烈的父亲
that was Andre's father,
还有我们的朋友泰瑞
and our friend Terry.
在难民营
At the camp,
情况越来越糟糕
it just got worse and worse.
人们都陆续离开
People were leaving.
不再抱希望了
People giving up.
但我没有
But I didn't.
那天我外出归来
I was coming back from a run.
看见围墙已经倒塌
I saw the fences were down.
还听见了嚎叫
I heard the moans.
一切都结束了
It was over.
麦克和泰瑞
And Mike and Terry,
事发时他们喝高了
they were high when it happened.
他们被咬了
They were bit.
我本可以了结这一切
Could have stopped it.
本可以给他们个了断
Could have killed them.
但我却任由他们尸变
But I let them turn.
我确保他们没法咬人
I made it so they couldn't bite,
没法抓人
couldn't scratch.
我给他们套上锁链
I tied chains around their necks.
这很疯狂
It was insane.
很变态
It was sick.
我觉得我是罪有应得
It felt like what I deserved,
牵着他们到处走  让他们提醒我
dragging them around so that I would always know.
结果我发现他们还能保护我
I found out that they kept me safe.
掩护我
They hid me.
行尸们无法辨认出我
The walkers didn't see me anymore.
我不过是另一个怪物
I was just another monster.
我的确是
And I was.
我
Me.
很久以来  我活得像个行尸走肉
I was gone for a long time.
但后来安德莉亚让我振作起来
But then Andrea brought me back.
你爸让我振作起来
Your dad brought me back
还有你
You did.
我看见你瞧你爸的眼神了
I see how you've been looking at your dad.
你没必要害怕我
You don't have to be afraid of me
或者你爸
or him.
那天他跟我讲
He told me the other day
他以我为傲
that he was proud of me.
还说我是个好人
That I was a good man.
我不是
I'm not.
-卡尔  -我现在更加清楚了
- Carl. - I know more now.
他想要我成为怎样的人
About what he wanted from me.
我努力过了  但是...
And I tried, but...
我还是摆脱不了这些想法
I still have these thoughts.
我不是他认为的那样
I'm not what he thinks I am.
我也是个怪物
I'm just another monster, too.
以防万一
Just in case.
终点站
Terminus--
火警安全门
抵达就能活命
those who arrive survive.
沿着轨道前进
Follow the tracks to the point
走到轨道交汇点
where all lines intersect.
十字路口处有地图
There are maps at the crossings
为你指明道路
to help guide you with your journey.
避难所欢迎你
Sanctuary for all.
社区欢迎你
Community for all.
抵达就能活命
Those who arrive survive.
终点站  避难所和社区
Terminus, sanctuary for all.
-欢迎所有人  -你好
- Community for all. - Hello.
抵达就...
Those who s--
你好
Hello.
肯定是艾伯特在放哨
Well, I bet Albert is on perimeter watch.
你们是来抢劫的吗
You here to rob us?
不是
No.
我们想在你看到我们之前  先来见你
We wanted to see you before you saw us.
有道理
Makes sense.
我们一般会在轨道交汇处欢迎别人
Usually we do this where the tracks meet.
欢迎来到终点站
Welcome to Terminus.
我叫葛瑞
I'm Gareth.
看来你们在外面漂泊很久了
Looks like you've been on the road for a good bit.
是的
We have.
我叫瑞克  那是卡尔  达里尔  米琼恩
Rick. That's Carl, Daryl, Michonne.
你们很紧张  我能理解
You're nervous. I get it.
我们也是一样
We were all the same way.
我们是来这里避难的
We came here for sanctuary.
你们也是吗
That what you're here for?
是的
Yes.
很好
Good.
你们找对地方了  亚历克斯
You found it. Hey, Alex.
这里不如前门好看
This isn't as pretty as the front.
我们倒是没什么可隐藏的
We got nothing to hide,
但是迎宾处比这儿看起来好多了
but the welcome wagon is a whole lot nicer.
亚历克斯会带你们过去  问几个问题
Alex will take you, ask you a few questions.
但是首先
Uh, but first,
我们需要检查一下你们的武器
we need to see everyone's weapons.
请把武器放到你们前面的地上
If you could just lay them down in front of you.
好吧
All right.
-相信你能够理解  -是的  我理解
- I'm sure you understand. - Yes, I do.
我可不想见到打你的那人
I'd hate to see the other guy.
是啊
You would.
-他们罪有应得吗  -是的
- They deserve it? - Yes.
只想让你们知道  我们不是恶人
Just so you know, we aren't those kind of people,
但我们也不傻
but we aren't stupid either.
你们也不该做傻事
And you shouldn't be stupid enough to try anything stupid.
只要有这点共识
As long as everyone's clear on that,
就没什么问题
we shouldn't have any problems.
有的只是解决办法
Just solutions.
好了
Okay.
跟我来
Follow me.
这个地方有多久了
So how long's this place been here?
差不多从一开始就有了
Since almost the start.
其他营地被行尸蹂躏后
When all the camps got overrun,
人们开始向这里汇集
people started finding this place.
我觉得这是人的本能
I think it was instinct, you know?
循着一条路
Follow a path.
有的人往海岸走
Some folks were heading to the coast,
有的人往西边或北边走
others out west or up north,
但他们最后都会来到这里
but they all wound up here.
听说你们是从后门进来的  真聪明
Heard you came in the back door. Smart.
你们很适合这里
You'll fit right in here.
玛丽  给这些新人点吃的吧
Hey, Mary, would you fix each of these new folks a plate for me?
你们为什么这么做
Why do you do it?
你们为什么欢迎外人
Why do you let people in?
越多人加入  我们越强大
The more people become a part of us, we get stronger.
所以我们才会设置标志
That's why we put up the signs,
邀请人们加入
invite people in.
这是我们的生存之道
It's how we survive.
给
Here.
不
No.
这表你是从哪搞来的
Where the hell did you get this watch?
-帕特里克  -格兰姆斯先生
- Hey, Patrick. - Hey, Mr. Grimes.
感谢你拿回来了这些东西
Thanks for grabbing these.
我以为卡尔会想要
Well, I thought Carl might want 'em.
它们放在那里
They were just sitting there.
半天也没人玩
I figured it had been a while.
虽然这是4到12岁儿童玩的  但我不觉得羞愧
I'm not ashamed that they're for ages four to 12.
你不该感到羞愧
You shouldn't be.
-卡尔  -嗯
- Carl. - Yes?
卡尔
Carl.
我需要你帮我个忙
I need your help with something.
放下吧
Leave it behind.
什么
What?
枪只会碍事儿
It'll just get in the way.
这表他妈的是从哪来的
Where the hell did you get this watch?
你想要答案吗  你想要别的东西吗
You want answers? You want anything else?
放下枪你才能得到
You get 'em when you put down the gun.
我看到你们楼顶上的狙击手了
I see your man on the roof with a sniper rifle.
他枪法有多好  这表到底是哪来的
How good's his aim? Where'd you get the watch?
-表是哪来的  -别轻举妄动
- Where'd you get the watch?! - Don't do anything!
一切在我掌控中  放下枪
I have this! You just put it down.
放下
You put it down!
你最好听我的话  我们的人很多
You want to listen to me. There's a lot of us.
这表是从哪来的
Where did you get the watch?
从死人身上扒下来的
I got it off of a dead one.
我觉得他用不上
I didn't think he'd need it.
那身防爆服呢  那个斗篷呢
What about the riot gear? The poncho?
防爆服是一个死警察的
Got the riot gear off a dead cop.
斗篷是在晒衣绳上取的
Found the poncho on a clothesline.
-葛瑞  我们可以等等  -闭嘴  亚历克斯
- Gareth, we can wait. - Shut up, Alex.
有话就对我说
You talk to me.
还有什么好说的
What's there left to say?
你不再信任我们了
You don't trust us anymore.
-葛瑞  -闭嘴
- Gareth. - Shut up.
-葛瑞  求你了  -没事的
- Gareth, please. - It's okay.
没事的
It's okay.
瑞克  你想要什么
Rick, what do you want?
我们的人在哪里
Where are our people?
你没有回答问题
You didn't answer the question.
卡尔
Carl!
伏身  快跑
Get down, now! Go!
朝主干道射击
Shots fired in the main.
往大楼方向赶
Heading into the building.
快
Come on!
这边
Here!
继续射击
Stay on your shot.
-快  这边  -把他们从B口赶走
- Come on, this way. - Get them off B!
-救命  -怎么回事
- Help! Help! - What the hell?
让我们出去
Let us out!
-救命  -继续跑
- Help! - Keep going.
救命
Help!
这他妈是什么地方
What the hell is this place?
我觉得这些人不是想杀掉我们
These people, I don't think they're trying to kill us.
再也不要
再也不信
是的  他们瞄准的是我们的脚
No, they were aiming at our feet.
我们永远在第一位
那边
There.
快
Go!
马上放下武器
Drop your weapons! Now!
马上
Now!
头领  往左走
Ringleader, go to your left.
火车厢那边  快去
The train car, go.
你照我们说的做  这男孩就跟你走
You do what we say, the boy goes with you.
不然他就要死  你也要死
Anything else, he dies and you end up in there anyway.
接着是弩手
Now the archer.
接着是武士
Now the samurai.
奶粉
站在门口  按照头领
Stand at the door, ringleader,
弓箭手和武士这个顺序
archer, samurai, in that order.
我儿子
My son.
去吧  孩子
Go, kid.
头领  打开门走进去
Ringleader, open the door and go in.
我要和他一起进去
I'll go in with him.
别逼我们现在就杀了他
Don't make us kill him now.
瑞克
Rick?
你在这里
You're here.
你们在这里
他们是我们的朋友
They're our friends.
他们救了我们
They helped save us.
好的
Yeah.
那他们就是我们的朋友
Now they're friends of ours.
可惜时日不多了
For however long that'll be.
不
No.
真乖  朱迪思
There you go, Judith.
真乖
There you go.
插进去的时候角度大一点
Put it in at more of an angle.
该给你弄一顶农夫帽了
Gonna have to get you a farming hat.
城里来了个新警长
There's a new sheriff in town.
-看上去如何  -很不错
- How's it look? - Looks good.
我们可以一直都这样
It can be like this all the time.
现在能这样
It's like this now.
已经够了
That's enough.
等他们发现时  就会觉得自己很蠢
They're gonna feel pretty stupid when they find out.
发现什么
Find out what?
他们惹了不该惹的人
They're screwing with the wrong people.